Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/mnguyentc (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Task Management Strategy Stakeholder Analysis

Languages

Vietnamese (Native or Bilingual) English (Full Professional) Finnish (Limited Working)

Certifications

Microsoft Certified System Administrator Cisco Certified Network Associate

Publications

Transition from IPv4 to IPv6: Best Method for Large Enterprise Networks

Minh Nguyen

Project Manager at Oivan Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

Open-minded, creative, and hard-working person with professional working ethic.

During the period of establishing and managing my own startup, I have gained many experiences in HR activities, marketing coordination, business intelligence, data collection and reporting.

Moreover, I am punctual, customer-oriented, and careful with the ability of handling stressful work under pressure. I am also flexible and adapt easily to new environment.

Experience

Oivan

Project Manager September 2020 - Present (4 years 7 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Oivan harnesses the strengths of the web, mobile, cloud, cybersecurity, and blockchain technologies to help our clients to launch transformative digital services. Our international team of digitalization experts manages digital services' full lifecycle, from design and development to operations and analytics.

IWA Ltd Project Manager September 2019 - September 2020 (1 year 1 month) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

fram^, Nordic Coder, Carmudi Product Manager May 2018 - August 2019 (1 year 4 months) Vietnam

Fram Ltd.

- Managed different stakeholders in connection with client projects from many countries in Europe and Asia.
- Produced product specifications and requirements based on customers' needs and desires.
- Implemented new product ideas and/or product changes.
- Controlled delivery of projects with best quality for clients.
- Planned, monitored, managed, and followed up on work results of each team member.

Carmudi Ltd. (a venture of Fram Ltd.)

- Managed a car-classified listing website with many sub products.
- Analyzed markets and competitors to propose product requirements and product development schedule.
- Provided information to the management by managing the roadmap, prioritizing product opportunities, refining feature ideas and maintaining existing features.
- Managed the process of developing a car inspection mobile app.

Nordic Coder Ltd. (a venture of Fram Ltd)

- Managed an online platform specialized in programming courses.
- Analyzed markets and competitors to propose product requirements and product development schedule.
- Provided information to the management by managing the roadmap, prioritizing product opportunities, refining feature ideas and maintaining existing features.

Weboy Design Freelance Website Developer January 2015 - May 2018 (3 years 5 months)

Helsinki Area, Finland

- Designed and developed customer website projects from various business industry.
- Developed strong and innovative digital marketing strategies, using SEO, PPC, and other techniques to drive traffic to customer pages and generate interest in company products and services.
- Portfolio link: http://weboy.fi/

Deli Piste LLC Managing Partner January 2015 - December 2017 (3 years)

Helsinki Area, Finland

- Established the first food delivery company to deliver from restaurants to individual customers in Helsinki.
- Performed all of business operations including marketing and sales strategy, financing, creation of company culture, human resources, customer acquisition.
- Designed and developed online ordering platform for individual and business customers.
- Organized and managed delivery team for Helsinki region area.

JobGo International Data Scraping Application Developer July 2014 - December 2014 (6 months)

Helsinki, Finland

- Developed job aggregator application based on PHP to acquire thousands of job advertisements from data sources and maintaining databases.
- Developed and implemented data collection systems, data analytics and other strategies to optimize efficiency and quality.
- Implemented testing tools that monitor the ongoing performance of the application.

Annatex Online Fashion Website Designer April 2012 - January 2014 (1 year 10 months) Thailand

- Designed and developed an e-commerce website for online fashion store using Drupal CMS.
- Performed SEO and created digital marketing plans.
- Monitored usage and performance and resolved issues as they arised.

Education

Axxell Monikulttuurisuuskeskus

Työelämän suomea maahanmuuttajille · (2013 - 2013)

Lahti University of Applied Sciences

Bachelor, Business Information Technology (2008 - 2012)

Fachhochschule Frankfurt am Main

Eramus Exchange, Business Information Technology (2011 - 2011)

Goethe Institut

A1, Deutsch · (2010 - 2010)